jobs = {
  "janitor": {
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "I DEMAND TO SPEAK TO YOUR MANAGER FOR SUCH A BAD CLEANING JOB",
        
        "response": ["i quit", "no karen", "why me", "boss theres a karen", "why is this my life", "no", "nah", "stop", "I'm gonna call the cops", "okay", "ok"],

        "right": ["no karen","boss theres a karen", "why is this my life", "no", "nah", "stop"]
      },
      {
        "question": "clean this 30,000 square feet abandoned mall in the next half hour or you're fired.",
        "response": ["easy", "no", "why", "omg", "how", "ok", "cool", 'sure', "yes", "nah"]
      },
      {
        "question": "which of building you want to care take of",
        "response": ['office', 'apartment', 'home', 'area51', 'ur mom', "house", "building", "you", "your mom", "u"]
      },
      {
        "question": "your mop is broken. what do u do?",
        "response": ['give me new mop', "quit", 'i quit','die', 'idk', "idc", "go away", "get another one", "get new mop", "gimme one", "give me another one"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be promoted?",
        "response": ['nope', 'hate promotions', 'nah', 'no', 'no thanks', 'demote pls']
      },
      {
        "question": "your shift is the basement",
        "response": ["yessir", "yes sir", "ok", "i love the basement", "best manager ever!", "yay", "nice", "awesome"]
      },
      {
       "question": "what do you want your salary to be?",
       "response": ["1$", "I'll work for free", "none", "you deside", "idk", "free", "I'm a slave"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 50,
    "salary": 100,
    "fail": 10
  },
  "developer": {
    "tasks": [
      {
        "question": "bruh you suck",
        "response": ["yes", "i am", "agree", "i agree", "ok", "yeah"]
      },
      {
        "question": "ERROR: You're not an developer",
        "response": ["ok", 'nice', "cool"]
      },
      {
        "question": "what does this error mean?",
        "response": ["search google", "idk", "idc", "ask someone else", "unknown", "hey google, thats this error"]
      },
      {
        "question": "how much google searching have you used",
        "response": ["yes", "no", "uh", "uhh", "uhhh", "none", "stackoverflow", "stackoverflow yes", "all of it", "too much"]
      },
      {
        "question": "do you need help?",
        "response": ["yes", "im fine", "yes please", "help me", "everyone like everyone", "ofc"]
      },
      {
        "question": "help the other dev",
        "response": ["tell him to help me", "ok", "no i hate him", "fine", "no", "nah"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 1000,
    "salary": 500,
    "fail": 100
  },
  "pilot":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "Sir, we're missing 20 people.",
        "response": ["don't worry about the losers", "idc", "fine, we'll wait", "they better get here soon", "i killed them", "don't care"]
      },
      {
        "question": "flight attendant: we have a code 432-45-34 A with a subcode 42-A150",
        "response": ["wtf", "wdym", "i quit", "what does that mean?", 'what?', "hey google, what does code 432-45-34 mean again?"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Sir I see some sus people?",
        "response": ["Call back up", "Stay calm", "Do nothing", "investigate", "Kick them out idc", "good", "call the fbi", 'police']
      },
      {
        "question": "Pilot we are going down! ",
        "response": ["I'm a profressional", "Okay", "Nothing to worry about", "everyone we are going down", 'Time to jump off', "I'm a pro", "calm"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Your co pilot has a gun",
        "response": ["Tell him to put gun down", "Be nice", "Knock her out", "Seduce her?", "take the gun", "kill him"]
      },
      {
      "question": "May day may day plane going down",
      "response": ["Call the nearest tower", "Yell", "start to panick", "Tell yourself it's fine", "Call your mommy and cry", "Its fine."]
      },
      {
      "question": "Someone is having a heart attack",
      "response": ["is anyone a doctor?", "Pray for them", "Try to do cpr", "Shoot yourself", 'Do nothing', "whats a heart attack?"]
      },
      {
        "question": "You see another plane approaching what will you do?",
        "response": ["Fuck no", "HELLP", "Nothing to see", "Call for others", "pray you be safe"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Excuse me Sir theirs a bomb on the plane",
        "response": ["Beg for your life", "Give them money", "Commit die", "Smoke",'find the person and kill them', "bomb squad get here rn", "calm", "panik"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 5000,
    "salary": 1000,
    "fail": 250
  },
  "police":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "a criminal shot you in the heart, what do you do to him?",
        "response": ["shoot him back", "shoot him", "kill him", "kill", "shoot", "shot", "nothing"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Did you just kill a person??",
        "response": ["No, I didn't", "Yes, oh boi your dead", "you can't stop me", "Not sure chief", "shoot", "Shoot the witness", "no", "idk"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Help, anyone there to save me??",
        "response": ["nope, save your self", "can't be bothered", "Run away from scene", "kill", "Inviestgate", "Void", "I do not exist", "call 911"]
      },
      {
        "question": "What will you do?",
        "response": ["Kill the armed robber", "Shoot near the legs", "backup pls", "Call for backup and wait", "Look the other way", "panik", "shoot"]
      },
      {
        "question": "[UNIT 427] officer down, need backup!",
        "response": ["Let someone deal with it", "Walk away", "360 no scop", "Respond to the call","Dream about being in the FBI", "*destroys radio*"]
      },
      {
        "question": "You see a suspicous person near lamp trump, what will you do?",
        "response": ["ignore", "Tell everyone", "Pull out de gun", "Do nothing", "Warn the public", "i don't care", "i don't care, never did"]
      },
      {
        "question": "You see a women shouting thief, what will you do?",
        "response": ["Run after them", "Call the police", "Hide away", "Get in the car", "Rob the women", "arrest the women", "call 911"]
      },
      {
        "question": "You hear a karen, wheres the manager, what will you do?",
        "response": ["Assist them", "Tell them to get a life", "Ruin her life ", "Assist the manager ", "expose her to the internet", "help karen"]
      },
      {
        "question": "you're being assulted, what will you do?",
        "response": ["Arrest them", "Curse them", "Pull gun on them", "shoot", "Perform a ritual", "shots fired", "assult them back", "pull out a minigun"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is older the police or the country of united states.?",
        "response": ["The police", "The country", "God knows", "Time to google it ", "Call a friend", "hey google help me"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 2000,
    "salary": 400,
    "fail": 144
  },
  "cook":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "OMG A RAT IN THE SOUP! WHAT  DO YOU DO!",
        "response": ["eat", "ignore it", "serve it", "get rid of it", "give it to your enemy",]
      },
      {
        "question": "The president of America wants dinner in your resturant, what will you do?",
        "response": ["Serve him", "Take a picture", "Put Laxative in the food", "Kill him", "throw the food at him", "poison the food", "demand money", "murder"]
      },
      {
        "question": "The manager of the resturants asks you to put poison in the food, what will you do?",
        "response": ["gimme promotion", "Expose them", "con him back", "blackmail him", "Do it",]
      },
      {
        "question": "Someone is offering you tip for the food, what will you do?",
        "response": ["Thank them", "Be ungrateful", "Be ungrateful", "Annoy them", "be karen", "demand more tips", "refuse tips"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Someone asks you, how do I get good as you?",
        "response": ["Cook", "Help your mother cook", "Ask for feedback when cooking", "Do volunteer work", "Do degree to be pro chef", "secret", "idk"]
      },
      {
         "question": "Which type of beans are used to make baked beans?",
        "response": ["Beans ", "Baked beans", "navy beans", "Bean inside beans", "Please stop",]
      },
      {
         "question": "What is the first rule of cooking?",
        "response": ["Cross contamination ", "Clean after cooking", "Have a sharp knife and a cutting board", "check if stuff is good", "Stubby stub", "poison your food."]
      },
      {
         "question": "You are offered to be in a cooking tournament for 5k dollars what will you do?",
        "response": ["Don't go ", "Go", "Ask your friends", "Ask your twin", "ask someone go for you", "no", "ofc no", "yes"]
      }
    ],
    "req": 500,
    "salary": 250,
    "fail": 50
  },
  "amogus":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "AMOGUS!!!!",
        "response": ["amogus", "nice", "sus sus", "sus"]
      },
      {
        "question": "a stranger said AMOGUS. What would you say to him?",
        "response": ["amogus", "shut", "shut up", "imposter", "sus", "sus sus", "die"]
      },
    ],
    "req": 10000,
    "salary": 1250,
    "fail": 1000
  },
  "soldier":{
    "tasks":[
        {
        "question": "You were shot in the heart, brain and you're still alive! but what's your last words?",
        "response": ["bye", "bai", ".", "ok", "ok boomer", "humm", "bye bye cruel world", "capitalism"]
        },
    ],
    "req": 100,
    "salary": 150,
    "fail": 20
  },
  "doctor":{
    "tasks":[
      {
        "question": "Your parent: BECOME A BETTER DOCTOR! YOU LITERALLY CANNOT DO ANYTHING",
        "response": ["ok", "ok boomer", "im trying to", "i am trying to", "i'm trying to", "no", "nah", "idk", "i quit", "you have cancer"]
      },
    ],
    "req": 2500,
    "salary": 1000,
    "fail": 10
  }
}